Guide to the Othniel Charles Marsh Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- General correspondence, 1814-1903; Series I
  - Mitchell, Silas Weir (1829-1914), 1888-1892; cuid957 (Box 23, Folder 941)
  - Mixson, J.M., 1890; cuid958 (Box 23, Folder 942)
  - Moffatt, George, 1890; cuid959 (Box 23, Folder 943)
  - Molthrop, William H., 1873; cuid960 (Box 23, Folder 944)
  - Montgomery, L.M., 1890; cuid961 (Box 23, Folder 945)
  - Montjoy, S.C., 1878; cuid962 (Box 23, Folder 946)
  - Moody, Eliza P., 1868-1869; cuid963 (Box 23, Folder 947)
  - Moore, Benjamin L., 1871; cuid964 (Box 23, Folder 948)
  - Moore, Charles, 1881; cuid965 (Box 23, Folder 949)
  - Moore, Homer, 1898-1899; cuid966 (Box 23, Folder 950)
  - Moore, James Edgar (1845-?), undated; cuid967 (Box 23, Folder 951)
  - Moore, James Miles (1837-1905), 1893; cuid968 (Box 23, Folder 952)
  - Morgan, G., undated; cuid969 (Box 24, Folder 953)
  - Morgan, W.W., 1869; cuid970 (Box 24, Folder 954)
  - Morison, George Shattuck (1842-1903), 1886; cuid971 (Box 24, Folder 955)
  - Morris, William B., 1874; cuid972 (Box 24, Folder 956)
  - Morse, Charles J., 1877; cuid973 (Box 24, Folder 957)
  - Morse, Edward Sylvester (1838-1925), 1873-1896; cuid974 (Box 24, Folder 958)
  - Morstatter, Jacob, 1866-1868; cuid975 (Box 24, Folder 959)
  - Morton, Henry (1837-1902), 1880-1885; cuid976 (Box 24, Folder 960)
  - Moseley, Henry Nottidge (1844-1891), 1883; cuid977 (Box 24, Folder 961)
  - Mosley, G.M., 1872; cuid978 (Box 24, Folder 962)
  - Moss, Jesse Lathtop (1847-?), 1869; cuid979 (Box 24, Folder 963)
  - Mudge, Benjamin Franklin (1817-1879), 1866-1873; cuid980 (Box 24, Folder 964)
  - Mudge, Benjamin Franklin (1817-1879), 1874; cuid981 (Box 24, Folder 965)
  - Mudge, Benjamin Franklin (1817-1879), 1875; cuid982 (Box 24, Folder 966)
  - Mudge, Benjamin Franklin (1817-1879), 1876; cuid983 (Box 24, Folder 967)
  - Mudge, Benjamin Franklin (1817-1879), 1877 January - July; cuid984 (Box 24, Folder 968)
  - Mudge, Benjamin Franklin (1817-1879), 1877 August; cuid985 (Box 24, Folder 969)
  - Mudge, Benjamin Franklin (1817-1879), 1877 September - 1878; cuid986 (Box 24, Folder 970)
  - Mudge, Charles F., 1876; cuid987 (Box 24, Folder 971)
  - Mudge, Mrs. C.F., 1877; cuid988 (Box 24, Folder 972)
  - Mudge, Mary E.A., 1877; cuid989 (Box 24, Folder 973)
  - Mudge, Mell R., 1874-1876; cuid990 (Box 24, Folder 974)
  - Muldron, H. L., 1885; cuid991 (Box 24, Folder 975)
  - Muller, Frederik and Co., 1887; cuid992 (Box 24, Folder 976)
  - Mulligan, John P., 1878; cuid993 (Box 24, Folder 977)
  - Munoz, Adolfo, 1883-1884; cuid994 (Box 24, Folder 978)
  - Murray, George C., 1870; cuid995 (Box 24, Folder 979)
  - Museo de la Plata, Director, undated; cuid996 (Box 24, Folder 980)
  - Nash, H.C., 1884-1886; cuid997 (Box 24, Folder 981)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1882; cuid998 (Box 24, Folder 982)
  - Neal, Stewart, 1873; cuid999 (Box 24, Folder 983)
  - Nebey, E., 1876; cuid1000 (Box 24, Folder 984)
  - Nelson, Edward T., 1874; cuid1001 (Box 24, Folder 985)
  - Nelson, John Young (1826-?), 1873; cuid1002 (Box 24, Folder 986)
  - Nelson, W.H., 1884; cuid1003 (Box 24, Folder 987)
  - Nesbit, T. Murray, 1877; cuid1004 (Box 24, Folder 988)
  - Nesbitt, E.G., 1872; cuid1005 (Box 24, Folder 989)
  - Neville, W., 1855; cuid1006 (Box 24, Folder 990)
  - New England Magazine, 1898; cuid1007 (Box 24, Folder 990A)
  - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad, 1898-1899; cuid1008 (Box 24, Folder 991)
  - Newberry, John Strong (1822-1892), 1866-1874; cuid1009 (Box 24, Folder 992)
  - Newberry, John Strong (1822-1892), 1875-1889; cuid1010 (Box 24, Folder 993)
  - Newcomb, Simon (1835-1909), 1878-1879; cuid1011 (Box 24, Folder 994)
  - Newcomb, Simon (1835-1909), 1880-1884 June; cuid1012 (Box 24, Folder 995)
  - Newcomb, Simon (1835-1909), 1884 July - 1885; cuid1013 (Box 24, Folder 996)
  - Newcomb, Simon (1835-1909), 1886; cuid1014 (Box 24, Folder 997)
  - Newcomb, Simon (1835-1909), 1887-1898; cuid1015 (Box 24, Folder 998)
  - Newman, E.S., 1889; cuid1016 (Box 25, Folder 999)
  - Newton, Edwin Tulley (1840-1930), 1889; cuid1017 (Box 25, Folder 1000)
  - Newton, Hubert Anson (1830-1896), 1891; cuid1018 (Box 25, Folder 1001)
  - Newton, R., 1884; cuid1019 (Box 25, Folder 1002)
  - Nichols, C.B., 1873-1874; cuid1020 (Box 25, Folder 1003)
  - Nicholson, Henry Alleyne (1844-1899), 1872-1880; cuid1021 (Box 25, Folder 1004)
  - Niemeyer, John Henry (1839-1932), 1881; cuid1022 (Box 25, Folder 1005)
  - Nightingale, A.L., 1874; cuid1023 (Box 25, Folder 1006)
  - Niven, William (1850-1937), 1898; cuid1024 (Box 25, Folder 1007)
  - Nolan, Edward James (1846-?), 1889-1891; cuid1025 (Box 25, Folder 1008)
  - Nolen, Andrew, 1870; cuid1026 (Box 25, Folder 1009)
  - Nolub, Ernst, 1895; cuid1027 (Box 25, Folder 1010)
  - Nordhoff, Charles (1830-1901), 1881; cuid1028 (Box 25, Folder 1011)
  - North, Frank Joshua (1840-1885), 1870-1879; cuid1029 (Box 25, Folder 1012)
  - North, Lute, 1873-1874; cuid1030 (Box 25, Folder 1013)
  - Norton, O.D., 1875; cuid1031 (Box 25, Folder 1014)
  - Nugent, William E., 1879; cuid1032 (Box 25, Folder 1015)
  - O'Brien, John S., 1896; cuid1033 (Box 25, Folder 1016)
  - O'Neill, Charles (1821-1893), 1892; cuid1034 (Box 25, Folder 1017)
  - Oppel, A., 1864; cuid1035 (Box 25, Folder 1018)
  - Ord, Edward Otho Cresap (1818-1883), 1873-1874; cuid1036 (Box 25, Folder 1019)
  - Ord, P., 1887; cuid1037 (Box 25, Folder 1020)
  - Orton, James (1830-1877), 1867-1872; cuid1038 (Box 25, Folder 1021)
  - Ortoz, J., 1874; cuid1039 (Box 25, Folder 1022)
  - Osborn, Henry Fairfield (1857-1935), 1889-1890; cuid1040 (Box 25, Folder 1023)
  - Osborne, James H., 1879; cuid1041 (Box 25, Folder 1024)
  - Outhwaite, Joseph H. (1841-1907), 1892-1895; cuid1042 (Box 25, Folder 1025)
  - Overton, James M., 1886; cuid1043 (Box 25, Folder 1025A)
  - Owen, Charles Hunter (1838-1922), 1890; cuid1044 (Box 25, Folder 1026)
  - Owen, Sir Richard (1804-1892), 1875-1883; cuid1045 (Box 25, Folder 1027)
  - Owen, Richard H., 1875-1883; cuid1046 (Box 25, Folder 1028)
  - P., M.E., 1874; cuid1047 (Box 25, Folder 1029)
  - Packard, Alpheus Spring (1839-1905), 1874; cuid1048 (Box 25, Folder 1030)
  - Packard, Lewis Richard (1836-1884), 1885-1894; cuid1049 (Box 25, Folder 1031)
  - Palmer, Edward (18314911), 1867; cuid1050 (Box 25, Folder 1032)
  - Parke, Charles, 1875-1876; cuid1051 (Box 25, Folder 1033)
  - Parke, John Grubb (1827-1900), 1878-1879; cuid1052 (Box 25, Folder 1034)
  - Parker, Francis Jewett (1825-1909), 1891; cuid1053 (Box 25, Folder 1035)
  - Parker, John D., 1867-1869; cuid1054 (Box 25, Folder 1036)
  - Parker, William Kitchen (1823-1890), 1879-1885; cuid1055 (Box 25, Folder 1037)
  - Patterson, C.P., 1878-1879; cuid1056 (Box 25, Folder 1038)
  - Pattinson, N.L., 1855; cuid1057 (Box 25, Folder 1039)
  - Pavlow, Alexsei P. (1854-1929), 1896; cuid1058 (Box 25, Folder 1040)
  - Pavlow, Marie, 1894-1897; cuid1059 (Box 25, Folder 1041)
  - Peale, Albert Charles (1849-1913), 1888-1889; cuid1060 (Box 25, Folder 1042)
  - Peck, B.F., 1884; cuid1061 (Box 25, Folder 1043)
  - Peck, T.C., 1894; cuid1062 (Box 25, Folder 1044)
  - Peck, W.A., 1867; cuid1063 (Box 25, Folder 1045)
  - Peckham, Stephen Farnum (1839-1916), 1879-1880; cuid1064 (Box 25, Folder 1046)
  - Peirce, Charles S. (1839-1914), 1881-1894; cuid1065 (Box 25, Folder 1047)
  - Penfield, Edward W., 1893; cuid1066 (Box 25, Folder 1048)
  - Penney, Charles George (1844-1926), 1894; cuid1067 (Box 25, Folder 1049)
  - Pepper, William (1843-1898), 1889; cuid1068 (Box 25, Folder 1050)
  - Percy, Harold, 1888; cuid1069 (Box 25, Folder 1051)
  - Perkins, Maurice (1836-1901), 1867-1868; cuid1070 (Box 25, Folder 1052)
  - Perrigo, George W., 1876; cuid1071 (Box 25, Folder 1053)
  - Perry, John, 1862; cuid1072 (Box 25, Folder 1054)
  - Peters, Christian Henry Frederick (1813-1890), 1887; cuid1073 (Box 25, Folder 1055)
  - Peters, William K.H. (1815-1884), 1880; cuid1074 (Box 25, Folder 1056)
  - Peterson, Olof August (1865-1933), 1889; cuid1075 (Box 25, Folder 1057)
  - Petich, Louis, 1898; cuid1076 (Box 25, Folder 1058)
  - Petrie, William M. Flinders (1853-?), 1879; cuid1077 (Box 25, Folder 1059)
  - Pettigrew, F.W., 1893; cuid1078 (Box 25, Folder 1060)
  - Phelps, George C., 1883; cuid1079 (Box 26, Folder 1061)
  - Phelps, M. Stuart, 1869; cuid1080 (Box 26, Folder 1062)
  - Phelps, William E., 1883; cuid1081 (Box 26, Folder 1063)
  - Phelps, William Walter (1839-1894), 1877-1889; cuid1082 (Box 26, Folder 1064)
  - Phillips, Andrew Wheeler (1844-1915), 1898; cuid1083 (Box 26, Folder 1065)
  - Phillips, J.W., 1885; cuid1084 (Box 26, Folder 1066)
  - Phillips, John S., 1898; cuid1085 (Box 26, Folder 1067)
  - Philips, L.E., 1887; cuid1086 (Box 26, Folder 1068)
  - Phipps, Henry (1839-1930), 1893; cuid1087 (Box 26, Folder 1069)
  - Phister, A.V., 1886; cuid1088 (Box 26, Folder 1070)
  - Phythian, Robert Lees (1835-1917), 1888; cuid1089 (Box 26, Folder 1071)
  - Pickering, Edward Charles (1846-1919), 1884-1888; cuid1090 (Box 26, Folder 1072)
  - Pilling, James Constantine (1846-1895), 1882-1883; cuid1091 (Box 26, Folder 1073)
  - Pilling, James Constantine (1846-1895), 1884-1885; cuid1092 (Box 26, Folder 1074)
  - Pilling, James Constantine (1846-1895), 1886-1887; cuid1093 (Box 26, Folder 1075)
  - Pilling, James Constantine (1846-1895), 1888-1890; cuid1094 (Box 26, Folder 1076)
  - Pinard, J. B. and Sons, 1883-1888; cuid1095 (Box 26, Folder 1077)
  - Pinart, Alphonse Louis (1852-1911), 1892; cuid1096 (Box 26, Folder 1078)
  - Pixley, M.S., 1888; cuid1097 (Box 26, Folder 1079)
  - Platt, Orvill Hitchcock (1827-1905), 1892; cuid1098 (Box 26, Folder 1080)
  - Playfair, Edith, [1883]; cuid1099 (Box 26, Folder 1081)
  - Playfair, Sir Lyon (1818-1898), 1883-1897; cuid1100 (Box 26, Folder 1082)
  - Pomeroy, Lucien, 1868; cuid1101 (Box 26, Folder 1083)
  - Poore, Ben Perley (1820-1887), 1883; cuid1102 (Box 26, Folder 1084)
  - Pope, James Worden (1846-1919), 1895; cuid1103 (Box 26, Folder 1085)
  - Porter, John Addison (1856-1900), 1897; cuid1104 (Box 26, Folder 1086)
  - Porter, J.W., undated; cuid1105 (Box 26, Folder 1087)
  - Porter, Noah (1811-1892), 1862-1885; cuid1106 (Box 26, Folder 1088)
  - Potter, William Bleecker (1846-1914), 1876; cuid1107 (Box 26, Folder 1089)
  - Potts, John, undated; cuid1108 (Box 26, Folder 1090)
  - Pouchet, Georges (1833-1894), 1893-1899; cuid1109 (Box 26, Folder 1091)
  - Poulton, Edward Bagnall (1856-1943), 1888-1896; cuid1110 (Box 26, Folder 1092)
  - Pourtales, Louis Francois de (1823-1880), 1875; cuid1111 (Box 26, Folder 1093)
  - Powell, John Wesley (1834-1902), 1871-1883; cuid1112 (Box 26, Folder 1094)
  - Powell, John Wesley (1834-1902), 1884-1886; cuid1113 (Box 26, Folder 1095)
  - Powell, John Wesley (1834-1902), 1887-1896; cuid1114 (Box 26, Folder 1096)
  - Pratt, Willard N., 1877; cuid1115 (Box 26, Folder 1097)
  - Prestwich, Sir Joseph (1812-1896), 1878-1885; cuid1116 (Box 26, Folder 1098)
  - Pruyn, John V.L. (Mrs.), undated; cuid1117 (Box 26, Folder 1099)
  - Puluffin, W.H., 1879; cuid1118 (Box 26, Folder 1100)
  - Purdy, F.S., 1888; cuid1119 (Box 26, Folder 1101)
  - Putnam, Frederic Ward (1839-1915), 1869-1888; cuid1120 (Box 26, Folder 1102)
  - Putnam, J. Duncan, 1877; cuid1121 (Box 26, Folder 1103)
  - Quackenbush, Leslie R., 1869; cuid1122 (Box 26, Folder 1104)
  - Quackenbush, V., 1887; cuid1123 (Box 26, Folder 1105)
  - Quatrefages de Breau, de (1810-1892), undated; cuid1124 (Box 26, Folder 1106)
  - Queen, James W., 1886; cuid1125 (Box 26, Folder 1107)
  - Quincy, Edmund (1808-1877), 1875; cuid1126 (Box 26, Folder 1108)
  - Quincy, Josiah (1859-1919), 1893; cuid1127 (Box 26, Folder 1109)
  - Rafferty, D., 1874-1875; cuid1128 (Box 26, Folder 1110)
  - Ramsay, Andrew Crombie (1814-1891), 1878; cuid1129 (Box 26, Folder 1111)
  - Ramsay, J.R., 1884; cuid1130 (Box 26, Folder 1112)
  - Randall, W.W., 1883; cuid1131 (Box 26, Folder 1113)
  - Randles, James, 1884; cuid1132 (Box 26, Folder 1114)
  - Rathbone, John Finley (1819- ?), 1893; cuid1133 (Box 26, Folder 1115)
  - Rathbun, Richard (1852-1918), 1888; cuid1134 (Box 26, Folder 1116)
  - Raum, Green Berry (1829-1909), 1882; cuid1135 (Box 26, Folder 1117)
  - Raymond, J.I., [1880?]; cuid1136 (Box 26, Folder 1118)
  - Raymond, J.W., 1871-1873; cuid1137 (Box 26, Folder 1119)
  - Read, W., 1882; cuid1138 (Box 27, Folder 1120)
  - Red Cloud (1822-1909), 1883-1897; cuid1139 (Box 27, Folder 1121)
  - Redfield, Charles and John, 1870; cuid1140 (Box 27, Folder 1122)
  - Reed, Anna E., 1880; cuid1141 (Box 27, Folder 1123)
  - Reed, Thomas Brackett (1839-1902), 1886; cuid1142 (Box 27, Folder 1124)
  - Reed, W.H. and Carlin, W.E., 1877-1878; cuid1143 (Box 27, Folder 1125)
  - Reed, William H., 1877-1878; cuid1144 (Box 27, Folder 1126)
  - Reed, William H., 1879 January - May; cuid1145 (Box 27, Folder 1127)
  - Reed, William H., 1879 June - August; cuid1146 (Box 27, Folder 1128)
  - Reed, William H., 1879 September - October; cuid1147 (Box 27, Folder 1129)
  - Reed, William H., 1879 November - December; cuid1148 (Box 27, Folder 1130)
  - Reed, William H., 1880 January - February; cuid1149 (Box 27, Folder 1131)
  - Reed, William H., 1880 March - April; cuid1150 (Box 27, Folder 1132)
  - Reed, William H., 1880 May - June; cuid1151 (Box 27, Folder 1133)
  - Reed, William H., 1880 July - September; cuid1152 (Box 27, Folder 1134)
  - Reed, William H., 1880 October - December; cuid1153 (Box 27, Folder 1135)
  - Reed, William H., 1881 June - April; cuid1154 (Box 27, Folder 1136)
  - Reed, William H., 1881 May - July; cuid1155 (Box 27, Folder 1137)
  - Reed, William H., 1881 August - December; cuid1156 (Box 27, Folder 1138)
  - Reed, William H., 1882 January - May; cuid1157 (Box 27, Folder 1139)
  - Reed, William H., 1882 June - August; cuid1158 (Box 27, Folder 1140)
  - Reed, William H., 1882 September - December; cuid1159 (Box 27, Folder 1141)
  - Reed, William H., 1883-1886; cuid1160 (Box 27, Folder 1142)
  - Reed, William H., 1890-1898; cuid1161 (Box 27, Folder 1143)
  - Reid, H.A., 1882; cuid1162 (Box 27, Folder 1144)
  - Reid, Whitelaw (1837-1912), 1879-1883; cuid1163 (Box 27, Folder 1145)
  - Reilly, Ben, 1875; cuid1164 (Box 27, Folder 1146)
  - Reilly, Thomas A., 1875; cuid1165 (Box 27, Folder 1147)
  - Remsen, Ira (1846-1927), 1882-1898; cuid1166 (Box 27, Folder 1148)
  - Retteys, C.V., 1879; cuid1167 (Box 27, Folder 1149)
  - Rhoads, W.W., 1876; cuid1168 (Box 27, Folder 1150)
  - Rice, E.C., 1871; cuid1169 (Box 27, Folder 1151)
  - Richardson, F.C.A., 1876-1877; cuid1170 (Box 27, Folder 1152)
  - Rida Sign Co., 1893; cuid1171 (Box 28, Folder 1153)
  - Ridpath, James, 1875; cuid1172 (Box 28, Folder 1154)
  - Riikimeyer, L., 1886; cuid1173 (Box 28, Folder 1155)
  - Riley, A.T., 1888; cuid1174 (Box 28, Folder 1156)
  - Riley, Charles Valentine (1843-1895), 1881; cuid1175 (Box 28, Folder 1157)
  - Ritchie and Co., 1862; cuid1176 (Box 28, Folder 1158)
  - Ritchie, Thomas P., 1871; cuid1177 (Box 28, Folder 1159)
  - Rives, G. L., 1888; cuid1178 (Box 28, Folder 1160)
  - Rizer, H.C., 1891-1894; cuid1179 (Box 28, Folder 1161)
  - Rizer, H.C., 1895-1896; cuid1180 (Box 28, Folder 1162)
  - Rizer, H.C., 1897-1899; cuid1181 (Box 28, Folder 1163)
  - Roberts, Benjamin K. (1845-1921), 1876; cuid1182 (Box 28, Folder 1164)
  - Robinson, Arthur, 1886; cuid1183 (Box 28, Folder 1165)
  - Robinson, J. (Dr.), 1876; cuid1184 (Box 28, Folder 1166)
  - Robinson, J.P., 1875; cuid1185 (Box 28, Folder 1167)
  - Robinson, Wirt (1864-1929), 1900; cuid1186 (Box 28, Folder 1168)
  - Roburtal, 1896; cuid1187 (Box 28, Folder 1169)
  - Rockwell, Charles, 1877-1889; cuid1188 (Box 28, Folder 1170)
  - Ruckwell, Charles Henry (1840-1908), 1882; cuid1189 (Box 28, Folder 1171)
  - Rockwell, George, 1874; cuid1190 (Box 28, Folder 1172)
  - Rodman, W.B., 1868; cuid1191 (Box 28, Folder 1173)
  - Roemer, Karl Ferdinand (1818-1891), 1867-1883; cuid1192 (Box 28, Folder 1174)
  - Roessler, A.R., 1876; cuid1193 (Box 28, Folder 1175)
  - Roessler, Paul, 1887; cuid1194 (Box 28, Folder 1176)
  - Rogers, Emma, 1882; cuid1195 (Box 28, Folder 1177)
  - Rogers, Fairman (1833-1900), 1879-1890; cuid1196 (Box 28, Folder 1178)
  - Rogers, George W., 1872; cuid1197 (Box 28, Folder 1179)
  - Rogers, H.C., 1882; cuid1198 (Box 28, Folder 1180)
  - Rogers, W.K., 1878; cuid1199 (Box 28, Folder 1181)
  - Rogers, William Barton (1804-1882), 1878-1882; cuid1200 (Box 28, Folder 1182)
  - Rolleston, George (1829-1881), 1880-1881; cuid1201 (Box 28, Folder 1183)
  - Roof, J.S., 1896; cuid1202 (Box 28, Folder 1184)
  - Rooney, Otis A., 1889; cuid1203 (Box 28, Folder 1185)
  - Roop, C., 1872-1874; cuid1204 (Box 28, Folder 1186)
  - Rossi, James C., 1896; cuid1205 (Box 28, Folder 1187)
  - Roth, Santiago, 1883; cuid1206 (Box 28, Folder 1188)
  - Rounds, T.P., 1884-1885; cuid1207 (Box 28, Folder 1189)
  - Rowe, T.K., 1874; cuid1208 (Box 28, Folder 1190)
  - Rowland, Henry Augustus (1848-1901), 1894-1895; cuid1209 (Box 28, Folder 1191)
  - Ruffner, E.H., 1877; cuid1210 (Box 28, Folder 1192)
  - Ruggles, George, 1874; cuid1211 (Box 28, Folder 1193)
  - Rum and Sons, 1868; cuid1212 (Box 28, Folder 1194)
  - Rumble, James, 1878; cuid1213 (Box 28, Folder 1195)
  - Russell, Charles Addison (1852-1902), 1892; cuid1214 (Box 28, Folder 1196)
  - Russell, [Charles Taze] (1852-1916), 1885-1890; cuid1215 (Box 28, Folder 1197)
  - Russell, Israel Cook (1852-1906), 1888; cuid1216 (Box 28, Folder 1198)
  - Rust, Horatio N., 1871-1876 July; cuid1217 (Box 28, Folder 1199)
  - Rust, Horatio N., 1876 August - 1880; cuid1218 (Box 28, Folder 1200)
  - Ryan, Thomas (1837-1914), 1897-1898; cuid1219 (Box 28, Folder 1201)
  - Saemann, Louis, 1865-1867; cuid1220 (Box 28, Folder 1202)
  - Safely, Robert, 1866; cuid1221 (Box 28, Folder 1203)
  - Sanborn, M.H., 1849; cuid1222 (Box 28, Folder 1204)
  - Sander, F., 1892; cuid1223 (Box 28, Folder 1205)
  - Sarchet, George B., 1881; cuid1224 (Box 28, Folder 1206)
  - Sargent, Joseph Bradford (1822-1907), 1890; cuid1225 (Box 28, Folder 1207)
  - Sartain, John (1808-1897), 1860; cuid1226 (Box 28, Folder 1208)
  - Saulmer, George E., 1898; cuid1227 (Box 28, Folder 1209)
  - Saunders, Frederick (1807-1902), 1887; cuid1228 (Box 28, Folder 1210)
  - Sauvage, H.E., 1899; cuid1229 (Box 28, Folder 1210A)
  - Savage, C.R., 1874; cuid1230 (Box 28, Folder 1211)
  - Savage, Joseph, 1872-1876; cuid1231 (Box 28, Folder 1212)
  - Sawyer, George F., 1877; cuid1232 (Box 28, Folder 1213)
  - Sawyers, James Alexander (1824-1903), 1873; cuid1233 (Box 28, Folder 1214)
  - Schafhirt, Fred, 1876; cuid1234 (Box 29, Folder 1215)
  - Schickler Brothers, 1864; cuid1235 (Box 29, Folder 1216)
  - Schierkoz, L., 1893; cuid1236 (Box 29, Folder 1217)
  - Schlaper, M., 1884-1885; cuid1237 (Box 29, Folder 1218)
  - Schonfeld, E., 1889; cuid1238 (Box 29, Folder 1219)
  - Schoonmaker, A., 1877; cuid1239 (Box 29, Folder 1220)
  - Schott, Charles Anthony (1826-1901), 1890-1891; cuid1240 (Box 29, Folder 1221)
  - Schowalter, E.R., 1869-1871; cuid1241 (Box 29, Folder 1222)
  - Schuchert, Charles (1858-1942), 1892-1895; cuid1242 (Box 29, Folder 1223)
  - Schumacker, Paul, 1877; cuid1243 (Box 29, Folder 1224)
  - Schuyler, Eugene (1840-1890), 1867-1871; cuid1244 (Box 29, Folder 1225)
  - Schwatka, Frederick (1849-1892), 1874-1886; cuid1245 (Box 29, Folder 1226)
  - Scleter, W.S., 1897; cuid1246 (Box 29, Folder 1227)
  - Scollick, J.W., 1889; cuid1247 (Box 29, Folder 1228)
  - Scudder, Samuel Hubbard (1853-1911), 1867-1891; cuid1248 (Box 29, Folder 1229)
  - Sealey, W.H., 1892; cuid1249 (Box 29, Folder 1230)
  - Sealey, Harry Govier (1839-1909), 1892; cuid1250 (Box 29, Folder 1231)
  - Seely, Henry Martyn (1828-1917), 1889-1890; cuid1251 (Box 29, Folder 1232)
  - Semenof, P. de, 1867; cuid1252 (Box 29, Folder 1233)
  - Semper, C., 1892; cuid1253 (Box 29, Folder 1234)
  - Seymour, E., 1871; cuid1254 (Box 29, Folder 1235)
  - Seymour, Horatio (1810-1886), 1869; cuid1255 (Box 29, Folder 1236)
  - Shaler, Nathaniel Southgate (1841-1906), 1892; cuid1256 (Box 29, Folder 1237)
  - Sheffield, Joseph Earl (1793-1882), 1876; cuid1257 (Box 29, Folder 1238)
  - Shelley, A.S., 1874-1877; cuid1258 (Box 29, Folder 1239)
  - Shepard, Carlos, undated; cuid1259 (Box 29, Folder 1240)
  - Shepard, Charles O., 1871-1872; cuid1260 (Box 29, Folder 1241)
  - Shepard, Charles Upham (1804-1886), 1868; cuid1261 (Box 29, Folder 1242)
  - Shepard, Charles Upham, Jr., 1869-1897; cuid1262 (Box 29, Folder 1243)
  - Shepard, James (1838-1926), 1890; cuid1263 (Box 29, Folder 1244)
  - Sheridan, Philip Henry (1831-1888), 1873-1887; cuid1264 (Box 29, Folder 1245)
  - Sherman, John (1823-1900), 1884-1897; cuid1265 (Box 29, Folder 1246)
  - Sherman, William Tecumseh (1820-1891), 1870-1888; cuid1266 (Box 29, Folder 1247)
  - Shufeldt, Robert Wilson (1822-1895), 1887; cuid1267 (Box 29, Folder 1248)
  - Silberrad, R. S. and Son, 1872; cuid1268 (Box 29, Folder 1249)
  - Sill, A. H., 1866-1867; cuid1269 (Box 29, Folder 1250)
  - Silliman, Benjamin, Sr. (1779-1864), 1857; cuid1270 (Box 29, Folder 1251)
  - Silliman, Benjamin (and Mrs.) (1816-1885), 1859; cuid1271 (Box 29, Folder 1252)
  - Silliman, Benjamin, Jr. (1816-1885), 1861-1863; cuid1272 (Box 29, Folder 1253)
  - Silliman, Benjamin, Jr. (1816-1885), 1863-1881; cuid1273 (Box 29, Folder 1254)
  - Silliman, Benjamin, Jr. (1816-1885), 1882; cuid1274 (Box 29, Folder 1255)
  - Silliman, Benjamin, Jr. (1816-1885), 1883-1884; cuid1275 (Box 29, Folder 1256)
  - Simons, R.B., 1870; cuid1276 (Box 29, Folder 1257)
  - Simpson, M., 1873; cuid1277 (Box 29, Folder 1258)
  - Sinnickson, Robert, 1882; cuid1278 (Box 29, Folder 1259)
  - Skilton, George S., 1879; cuid1279 (Box 29, Folder 1260)
  - Skilton, Julius A., 1878-1885; cuid1280 (Box 29, Folder 1261)
  - Slocum, John P., 1874; cuid1281 (Box 29, Folder 1262)
  - Small, Albert, 1884; cuid1282 (Box 29, Folder 1263)
  - Smedley Brothers and Co., 1876; cuid1283 (Box 29, Folder 1264)
  - Smith, A.C., 1879; cuid1284 (Box 30, Folder 1265)
  - Smith, A.J., 1869; cuid1285 (Box 30, Folder 1266)
  - Smith, Albert, 1876; cuid1286 (Box 30, Folder 1267)
  - Smith, B.D., 1872; cuid1287 (Box 30, Folder 1268)
  - Smith, Mrs. C.M., 1892; cuid1288 (Box 30, Folder 1269)
  - Smith, Hoke (1855-1931), 1893-1896; cuid1289 (Box 30, Folder 1270)
  - Smith, H.L., 1892; cuid1290 (Box 30, Folder 1271)
  - Smith, J. August, 1880; cuid1291 (Box 30, Folder 1272)
  - Smith, Mrs. J. Laurence, 1884; cuid1292 (Box 30, Folder 1273)
  - Smith, John T., 1870; cuid1293 (Box 30, Folder 1274)
  - Smith, Norman J., 1894; cuid1294 (Box 30, Folder 1275)
  - Smith, O.M., 1873-1874; cuid1295 (Box 30, Folder 1276)
  - Smith, Oberlin (1840-1926), 1890; cuid1296 (Box 30, Folder 1277)
  - Smith, Royal R., 1893; cuid1297 (Box 30, Folder 1278)
  - Smith, Samuel, 1873-1874; cuid1298 (Box 30, Folder 1279)
  - Smith, Samuel, 1875; cuid1299 (Box 30, Folder 1280)
  - Smith, Samuel, 1876-1877; cuid1300 (Box 30, Folder 1281)
  - Smith, Samuel, 1882-1883; cuid1301 (Box 30, Folder 1282)
  - Smith, William, 1874; cuid1302 (Box 30, Folder 1283)
  - Smith, William Manlius, 1877-1878; cuid1303 (Box 30, Folder 1284)
  - Smith and Sperry, 1874; cuid1304 (Box 30, Folder 1285)
  - Smithsonian Institution, 1899; cuid1305 (Box 30, Folder 1285A)
  - Smock, D. DuBols, 1869; cuid1306 (Box 30, Folder 1286)
  - Smyth, Egbert Coffin (1829-1904), 1870; cuid1307 (Box 30, Folder 1287)
  - Snook, Sam H., 1872-1875; cuid1308 (Box 30, Folder 1288)
  - Snow, Francis Huntington (1840-1908), 1879; cuid1309 (Box 30, Folder 1289)
  - Snyder, G.F., 1875; cuid1310 (Box 30, Folder 1290)
  - Somerby, H.G., 1863-1865; cuid1311 (Box 30, Folder 1290A)
  - Southwick, James M., 1887; cuid1312 (Box 30, Folder 1291)
  - Spaeth, P. Friedrich Adoloh T. (1839-1910), 1868; cuid1313 (Box 30, Folder 1292)
  - Spalding, James Field (1839-1921), 1867; cuid1314 (Box 30, Folder 1293)